const questions = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "What is 3 + 5?",
        options: ["6", "7", "8", "9"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 2
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "What is 10 - 4?",
        options: ["4", "5", "6", "7"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 0
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "What is 6 * 2?",
        options: ["10", "12", "14", "16"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 1
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "What is 18 / 3?",
        options: ["4", "5", "6", "7"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 2
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "What is 9 + 3?",
        options: ["10", "11", "12", "13"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 2
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "What is 15 - 8?",
        options: ["4", "5", "6", "7"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 3
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "What is 4 * 4?",
        options: ["12", "14", "16", "18"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 2
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "What is 24 / 6?",
        options: ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 2
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "What is 7 + 2?",
        options: ["8", "9", "10", "11"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 1
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "What is 12 - 7?",
        options: ["4", "5", "6", "7"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 1
    }
];

export default questions;